Mss.B.J44 Mss.B.J44
American Philosophical Society
- Papers
  - Letter to M. H. Jacobs, Philadelphia, May 10, 1938; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning forthcoming meeting of the American society of zoologists.
  - Letter to Theo[dora] Jacobs, March 26, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p.,end. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Cannot join a meeting.
  - Letter to A. H. Jenkins, New York, Oct. 2, 1930; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 2p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning eugenics.
  - Letter to Albert Johnson, Washington, Jan. 8, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    A.L.S. 1p. In pencil. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning immigration.
  - Letter to John C. Johnson, Gunnison, Col., Dec. 22, 1921; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p.,end. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Is interested in lecturing in Colorado.
  - Letter to Kegan Paul, Trench, Trubner & Co., London, Nov. 18, 1932; 8-1/2x5-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Agrees to their republishing a volume of his.
  - Letter to Kegan Paul, Trench, Trubner & Company, London, Jan. 28, 1933; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Suggests a correction in a publication if they republish it.
  - Letter to Vernon Kellogg, Washington, Jan. 29, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    A.L.S.with initials. 3p. In pencil. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning immigration.
  - Letter to Vernon Kellogg, Washington, Feb. 14, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H. S. Jennings papers.) Concerning immigration.
  - Letter to Richard Kimball, New Haven, Dec. 1, 1938; 8-1/2x5-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning his article.
  - Letter to Richard Kimball, New Haven, Jan. 14, 1939; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning the publication of their papers.
  - Letter to Joseph Wood Krutch, New York, Nov. 8, 1935; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p.and enc.of 7p.and printed copy of enc. Various sizes. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning a book review. Review printed: The Nation,vol.141,no 3677,p.748.
  - Letter to S. U. Lawton, New York, Jan. 26, 1933; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning a possible article on education.
  - Letter to S[hailer] U. Lawton, New York, March 13, 1933; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p.,end. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning a paper on education.
  - Letter to Bruno Lasker, New York, June 20, 1923; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    A.L.S. 2p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Typed copy. Will write a paper on immigration.
  - Letter to Bruno Lasker, New York, Oct. 6, 1923; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
  - Letter to Joseph Leidy II, Philadelphia, Dec. 10, 1923; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Thanks for drawing.
  - Letter to Joseph Leidy II, Philadelphia, March 19, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Will be glad to furnish him with reprints.
  - Letter to Carl A. Lohmann, New Haven, Jan. 24, 1933; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
  - Letter to Amy Loveman, New York, Sept. 20, 1930; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
  - Letter to Amy Loveman, New York, Dec. 29, 1930; 8-1/2x5-1/2, 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p.and enc.of 3p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Forwards book review.
  - Letter to Irene Mcculloch, Los Angeles, Sept. 5, 1944; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Asks favor.
  - Letter to H. C. Metcalf, New York, Jan. 24, 1928; 8-1/2x5-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning some of his lectures.
  - Letter to Maynard M. Metcalf, Waban, Mass., Jan. 3, 1934; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
  - Letter to W. H. Metzler, Albany, Nov. 19, 1930; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 2p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Answers question in genetics.
  - Letter to Adolf Meyer, Baltimore, April 20, 1931; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
  - Letter to R. E. Miles, Columbis, Dec. 4, 1930; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
  - Letter to J. Percy Moore, Philadelphia, July 17, 1939; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
  - Letter to C. Lloyd Morgan, England, Feb. 8, 1934; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    A.L.S. with initials. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Friendly letter.
  - Letter to Jay B. Nash, New York, Feb. 27, 1933; 8-1/2x5-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
  - Letter to W. W. Norton, New York, Dec. 17, 1930; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning a Spanish translation of his book.
  - Letter to W. W. Norton, New York, Nov. 20, 1935; 10x8; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    A.L.S. 6p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) ----Typed copy. Concerning his book, Genetics.
  - Letter to Henry Fairfield Osborn, New York, May 22, 1923; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S.Jennings papers.) Concerning an article of his.
  - Letter to H. L. Osterud, Richmond, Oct. 31, 1938; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning equipment for speeches.
  - Letter to H. L. Osterud, Richmond, Nov. 9, 1938; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Will check with Sonneborn at the APS meetings about equipment needed for speeches.
  - Letter to H. L. Osterud, Richmond, Dec. 8, 1938; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 2p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning equipment needed for speeches.
  - Letter to H. L. Osterud, Richmond, Dec. 14, 1938; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
  - Letter to H. L. Osterud, Richmond, Dec. 17, 1938; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning equipment needed for speeches.
  - Letter to Thomas Park, Chicago, Oct. 17, 1941; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings. papers.) Concerning the publication of his article.
  - Letter to Mrs. Maud de Witt Pearl, Baltimore, Sept. 28, 1942; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning a memoir on Raymond Pearl.
  - Letter to Fred E. Pomeroy, Lewiston, Maine, Feb. 14, 1946; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning his book, "Genetics".
  - Letter to William Procter, New York, April 29, 1921; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 2p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning one celled organisms.
  - Letter to Th[eophile] Raphael, Ann Arbor, Feb. 4, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p.,end. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) No statistics deal with Jewish immigration.
  - Letter to W. J. Rasbridge, Dec. 31, 1930; 9-1/2x7-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning a possible error in his book.
  - Letter to Revista de occidente, Madrid, Dec. 17, 1930; 8-1/2x5-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Hopes his work will be translated into Spanish.
  - Letter to revista de occidento, Madrid, Feb. 4, 1931; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Some other firm will translate his book into Spanish.
  - Letter to Hotel Richmond, Richmond, Oct. 8, 1938; 8-1/2x5-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Wishes to reserve room.
  - Letter to W[illia]m E. Ritter, Berkeley, Oct. 16, 1924; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
  - Letter to E.S. Robinson, Chicago, March 8, 1923; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S.Jennings papers.) Concerning a quotation in an early publication which is to be used.
  - Letter to Halle Schaffner, New York, May 13, 1930; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p.and enc.of 2p. Copy. Various sizes. (see H.S. Jennings papers Forwards book review.
  - Letter to Max Schoen, Pittsburgh, Oct. 6, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 2p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning education.
  - Letter to Alphonse Schwitalla, St.Louis, Feb. 4, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p.,end. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Friendly letter.
  - Letter to the Science Press, Lancaster, April 30, 1920; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
  - Letter to the Science press, New York, May 5, 1920; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
  - Letter to The science press, Lancaster, March 25, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
  - Letter to E. M. Scott, Boston, Nov. 25, 1933; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 2p.,end. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning genetics.
  - Letter to William D. Searle, Washington, Jan. 30, 1928; 8-1/2x5-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning an article to be printed.
  - Letter to A. Franklin Shull, Ann Arbor, Jan. 15, 1923; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning his lectures.
  - Letter to A. Franklin Shull, Ann Arbor, Jan. 21, 1923; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    A.L.S. 2p. Draft. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) ----Typed copy. Concerning lectures he will give.
  - Letter to [A. Franklin] Shull, Ann Arbor, Feb. 12, 1923; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p.,end. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Will lecture on genetics.
  - Letter to A. F[ranklin] Shull, Ann Arbor, Feb. 26, 1923; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Will be glad to deliver lectures. Refers to the APS.
  - Letter to A. Franklin Shull, Ann Arbor, March 8, 1923; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning lectures.
  - Letter to A. F[ranklin] Shull, Ann Arbor, March 29, 1923; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p.,end. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning some lectures.
  - Letter to D. Kerfoot Shute, Washington, Dec. 4, 1930; 10x7-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Thanks for his comments on his book on eugenics.
  - Letter to Geddes Smith, New York, Oct. 26, 1923; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
  - Letter to Geddes Smith, New York, Nov. 7, 1923; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Business of article on immigration.
  - Letter to Geddes Smith, New York, Nov. 9, 1923; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
  - Letter to Geddes Smith, New York, Nov. 21, 1923; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Article on immigration should be printed.
  - Letter to Geddes Smith, New York, Nov. 27, 1923; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
  - Letter to Geddes Smith, New York, Dec. 4, 1923; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
  - Letter to J. Whitefield Smith, Bloomington, Ill., April 27, 1933; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
  - Letter to T. M. Sonneborn, Bloomington, Ind., Oct.11, 1939; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 3p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Thanks for criticisms on his paper.
  - Letter to the stenographic office, July 28, 1944; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L.S. 1p. Enc.of 6p. Various sizes. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Wants copies of paper made.
  - Letter to the editor of The Survey, New York, Oct. 24, 1923; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning his article on immigration.
  - Letter to The Survey, New York, Dec. 12, 1923; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
  - Letter to The Survey, New York, Dec. 22, 1923; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
  - Letter to Norman Sweet, Fort Wayne, Ind., April 17, 1931; 8-1/2x5-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Thanks for publication.
  - Letter to John B. Thayer, Philadelphia, July 17, 1939; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Accepts invitation to participate in U of P bicentennary.
  - Letter to John B. Thayer, Philadelphia, March 13, 1940; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning the address he is to make.
  - Letter to John B. Thayer, Philadelphia, June 22, 1940; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning his visit for the bicentennial celebration of the U of P.
  - Letter to John B. Thayer, Philadelphia, July 9, 1940; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Forwards lecture which he will deliver at the U of P bicentennial celebration.
  - Letter to Frank N. Tillinghast, Oct. 19, 1920; 8-1/2x5-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Sends information concerning one of his publications.
  - Letter to Charles P. Titus, New York, May 3, 1921; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p.,end. (see H.S.Jennings papers.) Refers him to articles on the rotifera.
  - Letter to Margaret Wagenhals, New York, Feb. 17, 1931; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning genetics.
  - Letter to Henshaw Ward, New Haven, Sept. 11, 1930; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 2p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Friendly letter concerning genetics.
  - Letter to John B. Watson, New York, March 31, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning a lecture.
  - Letter to J[ohn] B. Watson, New York, April 5, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
  - Letter to J[ohn] B. Watson, New York, April 7, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
  - Letter to John B. Watson, New York, April 10, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning a lecture. Refers to the APS.
  - Letter to John B. Watson, New York, April 17, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p.,end. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning a lecture.
  - Letter to J. H. Weatherby, Richmond, Dec. 17, 1938; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
  - Letter to J. H. Weatherby, Richmond, Dec. 21, 1938; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
  - Letter to Blanche C. Weil[l], New York, Feb. 4, 1931; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
  - Letter to Blanche C. Weill, New York, Feb. 10, 1931; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Gives permission to quote from his book.
  - Letter to Winifred Willson, New York, Feb. 14, 1934; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
  - Letter to Winifred Willson, New York, March 19, 1934; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Hopes he can write an article for her.
  - Letter to Winifred Willson, New York, March 23, 1934; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p.and enc.of 6p.and copy of enc. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Sends article.
  - Letter to Carmen Wold, April 23, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Answers question on biology.
  - Letter to Yale university press, New Haven, Sept. 27, 1933; 8-1/2x5-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
  - Letter to the Yale university press, New Haven, Oct. 8, 1933; 8-1/2x5-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Asks copy of his book be sent out for review.
  - Letter to the Yale university press, New Haven, Feb. 19, 1934; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Orders books.
  - Letter to the Yale university press, New Haven, April 2, 1934; 8-1/2x5-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
  - Letter to Yale university press, New Haven, Sept. 20, 1934; 8-1/5x5-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Orders prints of his book.
  - List of persons to whom reprints are to be sent., 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    D. 14 items. (see H.S. Jennings papers.)
  - List of persons to whom the University of Pennsylvania should send invitations, [1940]; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
  - Miscellaneous items, 1943-1946; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Printed. 13 items. Various sizes. (see H.S. Jennings papers.)
  - Miscellaneous notes on paramecium bursaria, March 1, 1945; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    A.D. 4 leaves. (see H.S. Jennings papers.)
  - Miscellaneous papers pertaining to the World Government Convention, 1941; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    Printed. //items. Various sizes. (see H.S. Jennings papers.)
  - Memorandum concerning a letter to A.C. Giese, asking him to contribute a paper to a meeting, Aug. 9, [1938]; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
  - Telegrams to A.F[ranklin] Shull, B.M. Davis and Lenore Conover, Feb. 16(?), 1923; 11x8-1/2; Jennings, H. S. (Herbert Spencer), 1868-1947
    A.D.S. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Is ill and cannot give lecture.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Berkeley, March 4, 1942; 11x8-1/2; Jewett, Frank B. (Frank Baldwin), 1879-1949
    Typed L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Asks him to write biographical memoir of Raymond Pearl.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, March 19, 1942; 11x8-1/2; Jewett, Frank B. (Frank Baldwin), 1879-1949
    Washington, Typed L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning biographical memoir of Raymond Pearl.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Oct. 16, 1940; 11x8-1/2; Jones, Edgar Percival, 1896-
    Akron, O., Typed L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Asks for reprints of an article.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, Dec. 12, 1941; 11x8-1/2; Jones, Edgar Percival, 1896-
    Akron, O., Typed L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Thanks for reprints.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Oct. 24, 1939; 11x8-1/2; Jones, Lawrence Martin, 1902-
    Minneapolis, Typed L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Asks for reprint of an article.
  - Letter to Herbert S. Jennings, Baltimore, Feb. 1, 1939; 11x8-1/2; Josiah Macy, Jr. Foundation
    New York, Typed L.S.: Lawrence K. Froule. 1p., end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning his publication.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, March 14, 1941; 5-1/2x8-1/2; Journal of experimental zoölogy
    New Haven, Typed L.S.: Doris C. Rainey. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Accepts G.F.Gause's paper for publication.
  - Statement to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Sept. 1, 1919; 5-1/2x8; Journal of Philosophy, Psychology and Scientific Methods
    New York, Typed D. 1p.,end. (see H. S. Jennings.papers.) Business.
  - Letter to Herbert Spencer Jennings, Berkeley, Aug. 8, 1940; 11x8-1/2; Kaempffert, Waldemar, 1877-1956
    New York, Typed L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Asks for copy of his paper to be delivered at the U of P bicentennial celebration.
  - Account with Herbert S. Jennings for royalties, March 31, 1932, 1934; Kegan Paul, Trench, Trubner & Co.
    D. 6 items. Various sizes. (see H.S. Jennings papers.)
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Nov. 7, 1932; 10x8; Kegan Paul, Trench, Trubner & Co.
    London, Typed L. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Would like to republish one of his volumes.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, March 3, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Keim, Franklin David, 1886-
    Lincoln, Neb., Typed L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning a publication of his on genetics.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Jan. 24, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Kellogg, Vernon L. (Vernon Lyman), 1867-1937
    Washington, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning his article on immigration.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Jan. 30, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Kellogg, Vernon L. (Vernon Lyman), 1867-1937
    Washington, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning immigration.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Feb. 15, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Kellogg, Vernon L. (Vernon Lyman), 1867-1937
    Washington, Typed L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning immigration.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Sept. 29, 1938; 10x6-3/4; Kimball, Richard Fuller, 1915-
    A.L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning an article he will present.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Jan. 17, 1939; 11x8-1/2; Kimball, Richard Fuller, 1915-
    New Haven, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning his article.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Jan. 19, 1939; 8-1/2x5-1/2; Kimball, Richard Fuller, 1915-
    New Haven, Typed L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning his article.
  - Telegram to H[erbert] F.[sic] Jennings, Sept. 29, 1938; 6-1/2x8; Kimball, Richard Fuller, 1915-
    New Haven, Telegram. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning the title of his paper.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Dec. 29, 1933; 11x8-1/2; Kirkwood, Robert Ogilvie
    A.L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Friendly letter.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Jan. 31, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Kornhauser, S. I. (Sidney Isaac), 1887-1959
    Louisville, Typed L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Thanks for publication on immigration.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Oct. 18, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Korzybski, Alfred, 1879-1950